A hush comes over the crowd.
The only sound is Bender calling
everyone else a jerk as he swings!
Aw, he slices into the water!
Oh, man!
Boy, I'll tell you, man...
Bad news, everyone.
You're not good enough
to go on your next mission.
- Hooray!
- Not good enough!
Why? Says who?
Because. And says me.
It's an extremely dangerous mission
that killed my last crew,
and you're not nearly as good as them.
Whoo-hoo!
We live to suck another day.
Oh!
We are just as good as any of those
other crews you sent to their deaths.
What's the mission?
Collecting honey.
Ordinary honey.
That doesn't sound so dangerous.
This is no ordinary honey.
It's produced by vicious space bees.
A single sting of their hideous neurotoxin
can cause instant death.
And that's if you're not allergic.
You don't want to know what happens then.
No, no, no, God no.
Your insides will boil
out of your eye sockets
like a science fair volcano.
I didn't want to know.
These bees are larger than most Buicks.
And twice as ugly.
Larger than an American sedan?
Whoo, how big is the honeycomb?
Honeycomb's big... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not small?
No, no, no.
It'll take more than deadly, deadly bees
to keep us from doing our job.
Come on, boys.
But, Leela, we're no good.
Listen, I'm scared, too, but I'm more
scared of disappointing myself.
I'm not scared of that at all.
Now, bees communicate by dancing.
Like my parents.
Oh, wait, that was hitting.
So this language cartridge
will let you distract them.
Ah, good.
I often have thoughts and feelings
that can only be expressed through dance.
Bender, quick, waggle something.
Uh...
Leela, let's turn back.
There's absolutely no shame
in wussing out.
Relax. Everything will be fine.
Oh, my God.
The old Planet Express ship.
There's the black box.
Captain,
the beeshave us surrounded!
Oh, the professor was right.
We're not as good as his old crew.
Well, I aim to prove him wrong.
It'll take more than a few
deadly, deadly bees to...
Oh, Lord!
Uh, I couldn't make that out.
Too much static.
Ew.
We found it! The honeycomb hideout.
Hey, what's this goo?
Royal jelly.
They feed it to the queen.
Bees make honey and jelly?
Huh, how come nothing humans
make tastes good?
Help! I can't swim in jelly,
as far as I know!
Look.
It's a baby queen.
Aw, she's so cute.
You adorable wittle,
itty-bitty, fuzzy-wuzzy...
Leela, stop bonding and let's go.
I got jelly in my underpants.
I'm taking this bee with us.
With a queen, we can build a hive
and make more honey ourselves.
Let me just pack her a lunch and we'll go.
Pick up the pace, lady.
Uh, I didn't mean you're all fat.
This is where we distinguish ourselves
from the last crew.
Activate emergency
high-speed self-contained
escape pack crisis response units.
Quick.
Ow! Ow!
Good luck, Bender.
I'm back, baby!
We made it! We're alive!
Burn on that old crew.
The only things they did better than us
were suck and die.
Leela, we got lucky this time.
But you should be more careful.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
Thanks, but I can look out for myself.
Frankly, I can smell danger a mile away.
Look out!
If you want her,
you're going to have to go through me.
You call that a wound?
That's a boo-boo, tops.
But thanks for trying to save me, Fry.
Fry?
He's... He's dead.
Oh, who will make Bender waffles
just the way he likes them now?
It was all my fault.
He died because of me.
No, no, no.
I'm lying to make her feel better.
Husband, can't you go anywhere
without lighting something up?
It's an old Jamaican accounting tradition.
We burn his time card.
That way, his zombie doesn't come back
looking for his final paycheck.
He looks so natural.
It's funny to think he's crammed full
of sawdust and preservatives.
I only wish I could
have removed the stinger.
I barely knew Philip,
but as a clergyman, I have no problem
telling his most intimate friends
all about him.
Soothe us with sweet lies.
It may comfort you to know
Fry's death took only 15 seconds.
Yet the pain was so intense
that it felt to him like 15 years,
and it goes without saying
it caused him to empty his bowels.
Aw!
We now commend Fry's body to the ages.
He's walking on sunshine now.
This make me
the oldest member of my family.
Him do good snu-snu.
Eh.
All those times I said, "Kill all humans,"
I'd always whisper, "Except one."
Fry was that one.
And I never told him so.
Farewell from the world of tomorrow!
They say a spoonful of space honey
helps ease the pain.
Mm, it's good.
I feel funny.
"Ha-ha" funny.
Huh?
Leela?
Fry?
I thought you were dead.
Nope, I'm better than ever.
Before the accident, I couldn't do this...
Impressive.
But it does sort of support
my "You are dead" theory.
Then I'll prove I'm alive
by telling you something
only I could know.
There's a surprise for you in my locker.
I got it at a Swedish novelty shop
before we left.
It's too beautiful to open.
Can I open it?
Sure. There's just one thing
I want you to do.
What?
I want you to wake up.
Wake up? But I'm not...
In my dream, Fry said he hid
a gift for me in his locker.
If it's true, then he must
still exist in some form.
Of course he still exists...
As a frozen corpse in outer space.
I made myself sad.
Well, here it goes.
Oh...
Bupkes.
Well, I feel better now.
Pawning all the stuff in Fry's locker
helped give me closure.
Was there anything in there
that might have been a gift for me?
Nope, nothing.
Not at all.
No way, Jose.
Here it is.
You took this from Fry's locker?
Hey, the guy's dead.
There's no law against grave robbing.
That proves it.
Fry is alive somewhere
and he's reaching me in my dreams.
Bull pies!
Lay down here, and we'll do some tests.
If Fry is out there somewhere,
Leela's brain could be acting
as a five-pound Ouija board.
Is this some sort of brain scanner?
Some sort, yes.
In France, it's called a guillotine.
Professor!
Can't you examine my brain
without removing it?
Yes, easily.
Hey, what if Fry wasn't actually
dead when we buried him?
You know, like Julia Roberts?
Well, I suppose there's a slim...
I don't believe it!
What is it?
Is Fry alive in some
other dimension or something?
No! According to this gizmometer,
Fry is dead,
and nothing can bring him back.
Remarkable.
But my dream.
Your science can't unprove that.
How could I have known
the gift was in Fry's locker?
Easy.
He told you about it before he died
and your grief-roasted mind
blocked it out.
Are you saying
I'm going crazy?
No, no.
No one's saying that,
but I'm certainly thinking it loudly.
Hi, Leela. I'm just going to keep talking
even if you can't hear me.
Blah, blah, blah...
Shut up, I can hear you.
The professor says you're just a dream.
Oh, yeah?
Could a dream take you dancing
in a Venusian garden?
Well, yes, technically,
but it's still very sweet of you.
Then what if we shared
a midnight sleigh ride
across the ice fields of Hyperion?
Oh, Fry, you must be alive.
I've never been treated so romantically
by my own imagination before.
Here, take my jacket.
You look a little cold.
Thank you.
It's all so beautiful.
I forgot how many hundreds of degrees
below zero it must be.
I just wish I could convince
the others you're alive.
You can. All you have to do is wake up.
No, no, don't say that!
This is real!
Not another dream!
Fry's jacket!
The one he was buried in.
My dream was real.
He's alive!
Quit your bragging.
My boyfriend's alive, too.
Uh, not anymore.
That's better.
Fry's alive! I have proof!
- What?
- You do not.
I'm from Jamaica, the "Show Me" island.
So show me you blowing it out your fanny.
But he gave me his jacket. Look.
That's not Fry's jacket.
Fry's jacket is red.
That's your jacket,
an off-the-rack lime-green affair.
But Fry...
His jacket...
And when I woke up, it was on me.
You're under a lot of guilt stress, Leela.
Here, work it out.
I am not under stress, damn it!
Everything's going to be all right, Leela.
What?
I said
everything's going to be all right.
Uh... Maybe I am freaking out a little.
A little? You're screwier
than my Aunt Rita.
And she's a screw.
I need to calm down.
I better take some more
of that space honey.
You've been taking space honey?
Be careful, you purple-haired imbecile.
One spoonful calms you down.
Two spoonfuls helps you sleep.
But three spoonfuls
and you'll go into a sleep so deep
you'll never wake up!
Never!
One spoonful to calm me down.
Okay, I got a pretty good calm going.
Two spoonfuls to help me sleep.
Uh-oh... Still awake.
I guess one more spoonful couldn't hurt.
Ugh!
Oh, my gosh! I better get a sponge.
Fry?
Is that you?
I don't need a sponge.
Why am I sticky and naked?
Did I miss something fun?
Incredible.
According to the gizmometer,
Fry touched the royal jelly
in the space hive,
leaving an imprint
of his DNA and brain waves.
Then, when it spilled on the couch,
it recombined with
trace amounts of Fry's hair and skin...
And blood.
Don't forget about Fry's blood.
Yes, Bender, thank you.
In short, the various fluids
Fry left in the couch
caused the royal jelly
to regenerate his entire being.
- Neat.
- This is great.
My buddy's alive
and his credit cards are valid again.
Let's go get hammered!
I should warn you,
I'm a mean drunk.
- Fry, I'm so glad I didn't kill you.
- Me, too.
Feeling responsible for your death
was driving me mad,
but now everything is all right.
Uh, not everything.
What? What do you mean?
You have to wake up.
Wake up?
Oh, no... No! It can't be!
Poo.
I'm cracking up.
In my dreams,
I'm happy because Fry is alive,
but when I'm awake,
my mind plays tricks on me.
Aw, take it easy, Leela.
In every life, we have some trouble.
But when you worry, you make it double.
Don't worry
Be happy
The landlord say your rent is late
He may have to litigate
But don't worry
- Be...
- Happy
Ain't got no cash
Ain't got no style
Ladies vomit when I smile
But does Zoidberg worry?
Feh! You wish.
- Be...
- Happy
Don't worry now, Amy
Okay, I'm happy
Takes us home, Bender!
Don't worry
- Be...
- Happy.
Uh... Were you just singing?
No, I was telling you not to worry.
I'm not allowed to sing.
Court order.
I'll find Fry's coffin, get his corpse
and keep it under my mattress
to remind me that he's really dead.
That'll prove I'm not insane.
Okay, it's just an ordinary coffin
containing my ordinary dead friend
who I killed.
What happened?
Why am I in my apartment?
You killed Fry!
You killed Fry! You killed Fry!
Stop it!
- Stop it!
- You killed Fry.
You killed Fry.
Okay, I'm insane,
but I'm still sane enough to know it.
The only time I feel all right
is in my dreams, with you.
Three spoonfuls, then I can dream forever.
One.
Two.
Here goes.
Goodbye, waking world.
Leela, no!
Listen to me. You don't want to lie in bed
like a vegetable
and do nothing the rest of your life.
I've tried it.
Bedsores hurt!
Then what am I supposed to do?
- Fight it!
- I can't!
You can! The Leela I know
doesn't give up this easily.
Okay, I'll try.
Go away!
I don't know if you can hear me, Leela,
but there's something I want to tell you.
I love you.
I'm so scared, Fry.
I don't know what to do.
Just wake up, Leela.
Please, just wake up.
I don't understand what you mean.
Just wake up.
Please. Just wake up, Leela.
Fry... You're alive.
Leela, you're awake!
Of course I'm awake.
You wouldn't stop waking me.
- Where am I?
- In the hospital.
The ambulance took you here
right after the bee stung you.
But the bee stung you.
It barely touched me.
The stinger went right through me
and you got all the poison.
My new spleen came from a guy
who liked to motorcycle.
Vroom-vroom!
Sweet three-toed sloth of ice planet Hoth!
She's awake!
You were in the best coma I've ever seen.
The doctors said you'd never wake up.
Really? How long was I out?
Two weeks.
Fry never left your side for a minute.
And he talked nonstop.
Like a parrot of the sea, he was.
I thought maybe
if you heard a familiar voice
it might help keep your mind together,
but who knows if it really got through.
It got through, Fry.
It got through.
You could really use a shower.
You, too.